OK the first thing that you need to know when you're writing an email.
好的，您在写电子邮件时需要知道的第一件事。
The first thing you need to think about is that the style you use should not always be the same.
您需要考虑的第一件事是您使用的样式不应该总是相同的。
You don't want to use the same style for your friend that you do with.
你不想为你的朋友使用与你一起做的相同的风格。
For example a co-worker or a colleague.
例如同事或同事。
So always think about before you get started writing an email.
所以在你开始写电子邮件之前总是想一想。
Why am I writing this email.
我为什么要写这封电子邮件。
What's my purpose.
我的目的是什么。
What's the reason.
什么原因。
And then the style should follow that purpose.
然后风格应该遵循这个目的。
If you're trying to accomplish something for example by getting information you shouldn't ask a lot
如果你想通过获取信息来完成某件事，你不应该问太多
of questions about unrelated things.
关于无关事物的问题。
OK but you might do that if you're writing a personal email.
好的，但如果您正在编写个人电子邮件，您可能会这样做。
You might ask some more general questions and the email might be longer if it's more personal.
您可能会问一些更一般的问题，如果电子邮件更私人，则电子邮件可能会更长。
You might describe more things but if you're writing a more professional e-mail if you add a lot of
你可能会描述更多的东西，但如果你正在写一封更专业的电子邮件，如果你添加了很多
words that are unnecessary or you make a lot of extra points or say a lot then it's possible that what
不必要的话，或者你多加分，或者说很多话，那么有可能是什么
you're trying to get or maybe the question you're trying to get answered may be missed.
你试图得到或者你试图得到回答的问题可能会被错过。
So it's important to keep in mind that generally a more casual email will be or can be more relaxed
所以重要的是要记住，通常更随意的电子邮件会或可以更轻松
and longer and then a professional one should be shorter unless it needs to be longer for some specific
并且更长，然后专业的应该更短，除非它需要更长一些特定的
reason.
原因。
But the goal should be to try to keep it as short and clean and efficient as possible.
但目标应该是尽量保持简短、干净和高效。
So when you write a professional email try your best to be efficient.
因此，当您编写专业的电子邮件时，请尽量提高效率。
Don't waste space.
不要浪费空间。
Keep it simple keep it really simple when you're writing a personal e-mail.
保持简单 编写个人电子邮件时保持简单。
Or maybe one that's more casual.
或者也许是更随意的一个。
You can have a bit more let's call it flowery language.
你可以多一点让我们称之为华丽的语言。
Sometimes it's called flowery language you can use extra you can say what you want to say.
有时它被称为华丽的语言你可以使用额外的你可以说你想说的话。
You can tell a story whatever you want to do.
你可以讲一个故事，无论你想做什么。
So they're very different.
所以他们是非常不同的。
So the second one is to separate the purpose from the body.
所以第二个就是把目的和身体分开。
In other words the body of the email is maybe the largest section maybe you're answering someone else's
换句话说，电子邮件的正文可能是最大的部分，也许你正在回复别人的
question and the body is your reply.
问题和正文是您的答复。
Basically what you're saying but you want to know some things as well or you want to ask some questions
基本上你在说什么，但你也想知道一些事情或者你想问一些问题
in return you shouldn't mix those questions in with the body.
作为回报，您不应该将这些问题与身体混在一起。
If you're writing as a way to get something from somebody make sure that separate from the main chunk
如果您正在写作以从某人那里获取某些东西，请确保将其与主要部分分开
of the email make sure that's on its own.
电子邮件确保它是独立的。
So you have the you know you're answering their e-mail here.
所以你知道你在这里回复他们的电子邮件。
Then go down to lines and write your own question.
然后下线并写下你自己的问题。
That's what you want to know.
这就是你想知道的。
Don't mix it in over here.
不要混在这里。
If there are three or four questions mixed in with this then they feel the other person who receives
如果有三四个问题夹杂在其中，那么他们会感觉到接收到的另一个人
your e-mail feels exhausted.
你的电子邮件感觉很累。
Which question do I need to answer and they might just say I can't find all those questions.
我需要回答哪个问题，他们可能会说我找不到所有这些问题。
So it's very important to separate those and that's a general email tip.
因此，将它们分开非常重要，这是一般的电子邮件提示。
Now when you're writing a professional email you want to probably if you need something if you're asking
现在，当你写一封专业的电子邮件时，如果你需要一些东西，你可能想要
for something use a list.
对于某事使用列表。
We often say for example I would like the following.
比如我们常说的我想要以下。
So it's clearly separate from everything else.
所以它显然与其他一切分开。
One two three or dash dash dash and those don't even need to be full sentences.
一二三或破折号破折号，甚至不需要是完整的句子。
That's fine.
没关系。
So whatever you want to get from the other side the person you're writing to make sure that that is
所以无论你想从另一方得到什么，你正在写的人确保那是
clearly separated from everything else.
清楚地与其他一切分开。
Otherwise it may be missed.
否则可能会错过。
So number one make sure the style fits your purpose.
所以第一要确保风格符合你的目的。
Number two make sure what you would like.
第二，确定你想要什么。
The other person to reply to you about is separate from everything else in the email.
回复您的其他人与电子邮件中的其他内容是分开的。
If you have other stuff in the email maybe it's just that if it's a very quick email that's OK.
如果您在电子邮件中有其他内容，也许只是如果它是一封非常快速的电子邮件就可以了。
All right.
好的。
Tip number three if you're writing an email to someone you want to be careful about when you use dear
提示三，如果你正在写一封电子邮件给你在使用 Dear 时要小心的人
you probably know that some e-mails can begin with dear.
您可能知道有些电子邮件可以以 Dear 开头。
I want to say be careful with that.
我想说要小心。
When would you use dear.
你什么时候用亲爱的。
Well you might use dear if you're writing to someone you don't know for the very first time and that
好吧，如果您是第一次给不认识的人写信，那么您可能会使用 Dear
person has a higher status or maybe you have absolutely no idea who they are.
人的地位更高，或者您可能完全不知道他们是谁。
You just have a name you say dear.
你只有一个你说亲爱的名字。
Dr. Stevens.
史蒂文斯博士。
OK it's the first communication.
好的，这是第一次通信。
It's very formal or it's very close.
它非常正式或非常接近。
If you're writing a letter for example or a card to your grandmother then again you would use deer for
例如，如果您正在给祖母写一封信或一张卡片，那么您将再次使用鹿
that dear grandma.
那个亲爱的奶奶。
So deer can be used affectionately for for example relatives who were very very close to and deer can
所以鹿可以被亲切地使用，例如非常亲近的亲戚，鹿可以
also be used for very formal situations in which we don't really know the other person we're talking
也用于非常正式的情况，在这种情况下，我们并不真正了解我们正在交谈的其他人
to.
至。
However if you have an going relationship with them.
但是，如果您与他们有持续的关系。
You emailed back and forth regularly.
您定期来回发送电子邮件。
Don't use dear.
不要用亲爱的。
Just use Hi.
只需使用嗨。
And then the name.
然后是名字。
Hi Dr. Stevens.
嗨史蒂文斯博士。
Or just begin with Dr. Stevens.
或者只是从史蒂文斯博士开始。
Or you could say hello Dr. Stevens.
或者你可以打个招呼史蒂文斯博士。
Hello Dr. Stevens.
你好史蒂文斯博士。
OK so those are common.
好的，所以这些很常见。
Those are common.
这些很常见。
Now we could use hay but not probably not for Dr. Stevens.
现在我们可以使用干草，但可能不是史蒂文斯博士。
Hay is much more casual much more relaxed very casual.
干草更随意更轻松很随意。
So I just want you to be aware of deer and that it's actually not as common as many people who are learning
所以我只是想让你意识到鹿，它实际上并不像许多正在学习的人那样普遍
English may think it is our last tip is perfect punctuation.
英语可能会认为这是我们的最后一个技巧是完美的标点符号。
What does that mean.
这意味着什么。
So these marks we use is called a period.
所以我们使用的这些标记叫做句号。
This is called a comma.
这称为逗号。
These marks that we use when we're writing these are these are called punctuation.
我们在写这些时使用的这些标记被称为标点符号。
We use them to mark our sentences and I just want to say if you're going to write an email make sure
我们用它们来标记我们的句子，我只想说如果你要写一封电子邮件，请确保
it's grammatically correct English speakers tend to be very sensitive to things that are not perfect.
语法正确 说英语的人往往对不完美的事物非常敏感。
If it's easy to make them perfect writing that isn't absolutely clear all right.
如果很容易让他们完美的写作那不是绝对清楚的。
It's OK but if you for example write in fact and then you have a space here comma space here I'd like
没关系，但如果你实际上写了，然后你有一个空格在这里逗号空格我想
to whatever blah blah blah.
随便什么废话。
OK it's wrong it's wrong and it's obviously written by probably a non-native English speaker.
好的，这是错误的，这是错误的，显然是由可能不是英语为母语的人写的。
So all you have to do is learn the simple rules of punctuation and make sure that your email is perfect
所以你所要做的就是学习简单的标点规则并确保你的电子邮件是完美的
before you send it out.
在您发送之前。
There should be no space here.
这里应该没有空间。
There should be one space here.
这里应该有一个空格。
OK so it should be in fact comma no space.
好的，所以它实际上应该是逗号没有空格。
I'd like to add it's the same for a period.
我想补充一段时期是一样的。
If we end a sentence at all Let's imagine this is the end of a sentence.
如果我们结束一个句子让我们想象这是一个句子的结尾。
However comma space I.
但是逗号空间I。
OK.
好的。
So we have the end of a sentence no space here.
所以我们这里的句尾没有空格。
One space here OK.
这里一个空间OK。
And then however capital letter at the beginning of the sentence.
然后是句首的大写字母。
Very important if this is a small h.
如果这是一个小 h，则非常重要。
It looks like a text message very unprofessional.
它看起来像一条非常不专业的短信。
No space here.
这里没有空间。
One space here and then I and I again should always be capitalized.
这里一个空格，然后我和我再次应该总是大写。
We can't write it like that.
我们不能这样写。
So this kind of basic stuff if you're writing more professional emails and you're communicating with
因此，如果您正在编写更专业的电子邮件并且正在与
people by email with incorrect basic punctuation and maybe for example not capitalizing I could capitalize
人们通过电子邮件使用不正确的基本标点符号，例如没有大写我可以大写
not capitalizing I or the beginning of a sentence like that they might not read it.
没有大写 I 或类似句子的开头，他们可能不会读。
I often get emails from people and sometimes if I see that someone has not taken the time to carefully
我经常收到人们发来的电子邮件，有时如果我发现有人没有花时间仔细
read read through what they wrote and correct small things I go I think to myself This person doesn't
通读他们所写的内容并纠正小事我去我自己想这个人不
really care about communicating with me or else they would have taken the time to fix these are very
真的很关心与我交流，否则他们会花时间解决这些问题
basic these very basic things and they are very simple.
basic 这些非常基本的东西，它们非常简单。
All you need to know basically is what I just said capitalize the beginning of a sentence I and have
所有你需要知道的基本上就是我刚才所说的将句子的开头大写 I and have
no spaces before a comma or a period or an exclamation or any other mark and one space after.
逗号或句号或感叹号或任何其他标记之前没有空格，之后有一个空格。
So make sure to make sure to read through your emails before you send them download a plug in called
因此，请务必在发送电子邮件之前仔细阅读您的电子邮件，然后下载一个名为
grammarly.
语法上。
I'm not being paid by grammarly to say it.
我不是靠语法来付钱的。
It's a good plug in.
这是一个很好的插件。
It's a good app.
这是一个很好的应用程序。
You can you can download it.
你可以，你可以下载它。
I think for your computer.
我想你的电脑。
But you can also have it as a plugin for for example Safari or Google Chrome and GRC and them a are
但您也可以将其作为插件使用，例如 Safari 或 Google Chrome 和 GRC，它们是
they are why.
他们就是为什么。
It's awesome.
这很棒。
It can pick out the things that are incorrect and make your emails come across much more professionally.
它可以挑选出不正确的东西，让您的电子邮件更加专业。
OK.
好的。
So those are four tips to keep in mind when you are writing emails.
因此，这是您在编写电子邮件时要牢记的四个提示。
Now let's go through a couple of examples.
现在让我们看几个例子。